wilsonweb.com 2003-12-03

# Privacy Policy -- Wilson Internet Services

* * *

We respect the privacy of our newsletter subscribers, customers, contacts, those who answer our surveys, and those who fill out our questionnaires. It is our policy: 

  * **1\. Choice and consent.** To respect the purpose for which our site visitors gave us information. We give users choice and consent over how their personal information is used, and remove names immediately upon request. 
  * **2\. Third party use.** To not sell, rent, or loan our subscriber or customer lists to third parties for e-mail marketing. While we sell advertising in our e-mail publications to other companies, we never allow third parties any other use of these subscriber lists.  
We have partnered with NetCreations to build targeted double-opt-in e-mail lists for third-party advertisements for those site visitors who specifically request it, and no others. In no case are these double opt-in e-mail addresses ever divulged to advertisers, but strictly and ethically e-mailed only by NetCreations, and their company PostMaster Direct. 
  * **3\. Unsubscriptions.** To send our periodicals only to those who request them (that is, opt-in). We immediately unsubscribe those who request it through convenient unsubscribe links in every e-mailing. Our welcome message to subscribers and every issue of our newsletters clearly explain how to unsubscribe. We keep our subscription lists as clean as possible to prevent obsolete e-mail addresses to take unnecessary bandwidth. 
  * **4\. Cookies.** To use cookies in a responsible manner to help our visitors, not snoop on them. We use cookies (1) to help rotate banner advertising, (2) to identify shoppers with their shopping carts, (3) to make it easy to order a second time, (4) to allow subscribers to store passwords in cookies if they desire, and (5) to give proper credit for sales made through links on our affiliates' sites. We do NOT collect or use information from cookies to develop a profile about our visitors or shoppers. 
  * **5\. Security.** To store subscriber and password files with personal information in a secure manner. We store such files in areas not accessible to Web browsers, behind password protection, or off-line. 
  * **6\. Termination**. To continue this policy beyond the termination of our company. If a majority portion of the assets of our company were to be acquired by another organization, that might include our subscriber and other lists, but only as part of a clear agreement binding that organization to abide by the spirit and letter of our privacy policy. 

These policies apply to all websites owned by Wilson Internet Services and Joyful Heart Ministries, including wilsonweb.com, doctorebiz.com, netassisted.com, joyfulheart.com, and jesuswalk.com. If you have any concerns or questions about our privacy policy or information collected on our sites, please contact Dr. Ralph F. Wilson at [rfwilson@wilsonweb.com](mailto:rfwilson@wilsonweb.com?subject=Privacy_Policy) and he will reply promptly.  For assistance in developing a privacy policy for your own site check out the [Direct Marketing Association](http://www.the-dma.org/library/privacy/) site.  **Need to understand Web marketing?** [Try my web seminar.](http://wilsonweb.com/a/go.to/bot_link/http://www.wilsonweb.com/webinar/dre_sem/?c1=botlink&source=webinar&kw=dre_sem)

Sponsored Links| 

---|---  
Link Pop. |  [Aggressive link popularity services. PatrickGavin.com](http://wilsonweb.com/go/to.cgi?l=gavin_splink)  
Positioning |  [Answers from search engine reps, The Essential Guide](http://www.wilsonweb.com/afd/se_report.htm?splinks)  
Email Boost |  [E-MAIL MARKETING HANDBOOK gives you the big picture](http://wilsonweb.com/ebooks/handbook.htm?splinks)  
Conversion |  [TRIPLE your conversion rate with a great landing page](http://wilsonweb.com/ebooks/landing.htm?splinks)  
No money? |  [Here's how to start an online business on a SHOESTRING](http://wilsonweb.com/ebooks/shoestring.htm?splinks)  
  
**Wilson Internet Services**  
http://www.wilsonweb.com 

Copyright © 1996-2003 by Ralph F. Wilson, all rights reserved. Text, graphics, and HTML code are protected by [US and International Copyright Laws](http://www.wilsonweb.com/copyright/), and may not be copied, [reprinted](http://www.wilsonweb.com/copyright/reprints.htm), published, translated, hosted, or otherwise distributed by any means without explicit permission. [Trademarks and terms of use](http://www.wilsonweb.com/copyright/terms.htm).
